[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "Apple",
    "back" : "Яблоко"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "front": "Black",
    "back" : "Чёрный"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "front": "Car",
    "back" : "Машина"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "front": "President",
    "back" : "Президент"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "front": "Russia",
    "back" : "Россия"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "front": "Metallica",
    "back" : "Металлика"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "front": "Anthrax",
    "back" : "Антракс"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "front": "Pantera",
    "back" : "Пантера"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "front": "Gemini Syndrome",
    "back" : "Синдром близнецов"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "front": "Motorhead",
    "back" : "Моторхэд"
  }
]